<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
 	<channel>
		<title>2006 | Mighty Cheese | Colin Summers</title>
		<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/</link>
		<description></description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 15:01:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Sandvox Pro 1.6.2</generator>
		<item>
			<title>mon dec 25 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morning opening presents was great. Being with Nell, the boys, and their cousins was all fun. Taking the three youngest to Charlotte's Web and handling them for lunch was easy. We met up with Nell's brother Ted and his family. Again, all without stress. Then we were meant to go to friends' for dinner, with all of the above family and two other families (and their kids). That seemed like too high stress. I took half a dose of Vicodin and I was fine. Never felt stoned, never had the feeling of a headache coming. No problem sleeping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2006 16:27:39 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>thu dec 21 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_2.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Went to Las Vegas. Should have had more water on the flight. Should have eaten better, planned more. Who knows. Midway through the day, after a visit to the Slammer I knew I was in trouble. Stupidly, I didn't have my computer bag with me, so I didn't have anything to take. The meeting at the Castle went two and half hours instead of twenty minutes. I tried to rest on the flight home. When I got back to house I was already feeling a headache in the base of my skull, so I took half a dose of Vicodin. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn't feel stoned, but I felt drifty during some of the night's sleep. I felt some of the headache try to get through and I was really glad not to have to take a full dose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2006 16:27:34 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_2.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sun dec 10 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_3.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The annual dinner for our little investment club was tonight. I spent the day fielding questions about my parents' loft and helping my business partner deal with the memo we needed to send the contractor. I took half a dose of Vicodin before going to the dinner at 7pm. It lasted until 11pm. I never felt stoned or loopy at the dinner, but once I lay down to go to sleep I felt drifty, the room spun a little, and I had trouble sleeping. (The opiate does that. I go into a nodding state of dreaming often, but not really sleeping.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2006 21:54:44 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_3.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>fri dec 8 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_4.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We went to a huge (hundreds of people) holiday party. I hadn't slept well the night before and felt edgy and tongue-trembly. I took half a Vicodin dose and was fine the entire evening. I never felt loopy, but didn't get a headache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2006 09:24:24 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_4.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sat nov 18 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_5.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boys had a bit of a busy weekend planned. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We dropped Dexter for a movie and dinner with H. Rudy was dropped for a birthday dinner with a different H. Nell and I went to the promenade and tried on jeans and the fluorescent lighting and unhelpful staff in the places we went into started to give me a little headache. We picked Rudy up and went to our friends' the B's for dinner and desserts. While there I started to feel worse. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a few guests that seemed extraordinary. A woman with way too much money complained about how horrible it was that terrorists would target the beauty of cities like Los Angeles and New York. She seemed beyond belief, not a real character. Then the big muscle guy arrived with his little white poodle. I was trying to track everyone. It was impossible. The kids were shrieking. At about 8:15 I knew I had to leave. At 8:30 I told Nell I had to walk home, leaving her and Rudy there. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The walk was nice. It was dark, cool, and a little damp. I lost sense of time. As soon as I was home I took two Vicodin. They took over an hour to take effect because of the amount of food in my belly. I lay on the bed while Nell came home, made a phone call, got Rudy into bed and so forth. Finally, at about 10:00 the Vicodin took effect and I watched a little of The Hulk with Rudy before he went to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I slept fitfully, in bits and pieces, waking constantly until 2:45am. Then I was only up every fifteen minutes until 5:45am when I feel completely asleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning I felt awful. Particularly wiped out and hollow. I cancelled any thought of going flying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2006 22:20:37 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_5.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>thu nov 9 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_6.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I attended the get together for Rudy's class parents. Nell was meant to meet me there. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They all seemed like very nice people, but trying to keep names and faces straight for two and a half hours is a strain. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Half dose of Vicodin. No migraine yet, half an hour later. I would like to not have one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2006 22:30:04 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_6.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>mon mar 13 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_17.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Text message to Nell:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;argh. nearly instant migraine. i will be heading home soon.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Almost certainly written from Las Vegas.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br class=&quot;webkit-block-placeholder&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 21:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_17.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>wed apr 7 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_16.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-style-span&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-style-span&quot; style=&quot;font-style: italic;&quot;&gt;To Dean in mail:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-style-span&quot;&gt;&quot;First migraine of 2006! The Vicodin isn't working!&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 21:25:41 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_16.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sat may 29 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_15.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not sure. Gary Stockdale mentions in email on the following day &quot;I hope you got rid of your migraine.&quot; If it was bad enough to mention to him them it was bad enough that I probably took something for it, most likely a Vicodin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 21:24:14 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_15.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sat jul 17 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_14.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;i&gt;To Nell in mail:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seemed like you were extra nice to me last night, and I thought it was because you knew I was trying to avoid a headache (nearly successful, I had sort of half a headache through the Vicodin. Being a little dopey was better than being crushed by the pain, though, and this morning I don't really feel like I had a migraine last night, which is an improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 21:22:33 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_14.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>tue oct 31 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_7.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had the LaZebniks, Dellaversons, and Raimis over for pre-trick-r-treat. It was great. Then the food was delayed, two people came along as guests of the guests, Dexter had an unannounced play date which lasted until we had guests arriving...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt my blood pressure rising. So I took half a dose of Vicodin, which is my new plan. I tried Advil once, and that didn't work (there's no pain for it to block). I have a feeling that blood pressure medication would also help, and that Valium (or whatever the modern equivalent is) would work too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like I almost have enough data to show a doctor. I believe I take two Vicodin a month on average.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 20:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_7.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sat oct 28 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_8.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I didn't realize that I was going to be in the sun, dealing with a hundred strangers, and working retail. So I took a Vicodin before heading down to the Franklin Halloween Festival. Last three years I have returned and napped through a slight headache. This year I feel okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just wonder if a Valium would be better. I feel no effects at all from the Vicodin, I just don't have a headache and I'm not stressed out from the two hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2006 12:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_8.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sun oct 1 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_9.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a long day. There was a play date for Rudy and Haskell in the morning, lunch with Justin Lazard (an old, troubled friend), and dinner with the LaZebniks and Mel &amp;amp; Lilla in the evening (starting in the late afternoon). After fielding some scheduling issues (Nell running out just as her father arrived, Dexter not wanting to play even though Annie was there, Rudy wanting to read instead of engaging with Johnny), I went to get the ribs with Mel. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On my return, even after a relaxing walk to the store for beverages, I could tell that it was a headache event, so I took half a Vicodin. I didn't get sweaty, nauseous, or stoned feeling. I didn't get even a hint of a headache. It is 10pm and I feel a little more sleepy than usual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2006 21:55:17 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_9.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>sat sep 9 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_11.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-style-span&quot;&gt;Nell read in the NY Times that the latest study showed the management of migraines with a dose of something (Vicodin, Valium) &lt;span class=&quot;Apple-style-span&quot; style=&quot;font-style: italic;&quot;&gt;before&lt;/span&gt; the onset meant for a much better overall experience. I have noticed this myself, but it makes me feel like a drug addict, because I am taking an opiate before I have any real pain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nell's sister was having a big party (two hundred people) to celebrate the publication of her second novel. We got baby sitting and went. There would be a ton of people there who I sort of knew, but knew that I would have trouble remember the names of or talking to. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did remarkably well and it was only two hours into it that I started to feel a migraine start to sneak up. I went to the bathroom, took a Vicodin and was fine for the rest of the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 22:11:04 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_11.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>tue aug 15 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_13.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning from the Lake in Canada is an olympic event. I am responsible for both boys, there is a tight schedule, and I'm going through airport security &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; customs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was horrible traffic coming into Toronto on Monday night. We had a reservation at the revolving restaurant, and it took us so long to get to the hotel that I was worried we would miss the dinner time. The boys were great, but I seemed to have lost my long pants. I had to get them both bathed, and they were a little dazed from the car ride down. Traffic into downtown Toronto was terrible, apparently I had coincided with the global AIDS conference. Excellent. We parked and wandered the base of the CN Tower in fog trying to find the way up. Dinner was magnificent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We returned to the hotel and the boys went to sleep after a movie. I was up most of the night thinking about the things I needed to do on my return and how I was going to get home. What I needed to bring to the airport for the boys and what they were going to be doing on the flight home. I could feel the migraine at the base of my skull, but I willed it away. I couldn't have one &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; take care of the boys, so I decided I would just relax and focus and not have it until I was on the airplane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next morning it was a bums rush to the airport with a poor breakfast in a pastry shop next to the hotel. Canada, the can't do country. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We made it there, returned the car, stood in line, got boarding passes, stood in line, ignored the fascists, stood in line... Learned that we could not bring bottles of water onto the plane. Stood in line. I felt the migraine coming like a train down the line from the next town. I took a Vicodin so that it would not stop at &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; town. We boarded the plane. I had a bad ten minutes of sweating and nausea, which seemed to be from the Vicodin, and then I was fine (but a little stoned) for the rest of the trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 21:49:14 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_13.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>mon aug 28 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_12.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I flew to Las Vegas to look at the two projects there. The Castle looked great. The Slammer's Cellblock B addition is nearly complete. The interior decoration, in places, totally obscures the design intentions I had for the space. I am probably the only person who will notice. The clients are happy with the project, the contractor seems pleased with his work, the interior decorator is proud of what he has done... it's just me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I called Nell while returning to the airport and broke down on the phone. That was unusual. I stayed in the air-conditioned terminal for a short while planning my flight home and determining if I was okay to fly myself. I decided that the distraction of the piloting task was a good thing, and that if it wasn't, I would easily have twenty minutes to get to an airport if I needed to stop flying. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I flew home and I could feel all the little pieces of space definition that I like to see blinking off. I took a Vicodin and lay down. I spent some time with the boys and with Nell and went to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 21:43:08 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_12.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>mon sep 25 2006</title>
			<link>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_10.html</link>
			<description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I might not have eaten well enough on Sunday. An almond croissant in the morning, a Jamba Juice, a Koo Koo Roo Cookie... I bet I didn't eat enough. But it was an easy day mostly of being with Dexter. When I was going to sleep around 10:30pm I had a slight headache. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I woke up around 2:30am with more than a slight headache. It seemed like it might become a migraine. My tongue felt funny. I was too sleepy to know if my vision was off or if I was losing vocabulary (two other good indicators). I thought I might need to have some calories, something in my stomach. I went and had a few spoonfuls of Cherry Garcia, read Wired magazine a little, and got back into bed around 3:15am. I drifted off the sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I woke up at 6:05am and turned off my alarm. The headache was already bad and it was a relief to slip back into sleep. Nell's alarm went off a little later and I decided to try a hot shower. It didn't work. I gave up and took a Vicodin at 7:15am. Sometime around 7:40am I felt the pressure dissipate, or at least the pain was masked. I lost most of the usual things I lose when I get a migraine. The worst part is that my reaction to the Vicodin seems to be getting worse. I used to just feel warm and cozy and the pain would go away. Now I almost always have a fifteen minute period of nausea. This morning I lay down on the couch for about half an hour.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was loopy until a little after lunch and didn't drive. I wasn't that useful at the office. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Vicodin worked and killed the pain, but it was still a bad headache. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's the first time I can remember waking up with a migraine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 21:29:32 -0700</pubDate>
			<guid>http://mightycheese.com/migraines/m2006/untitled_text_10.html</guid>
		</item>
 	</channel>
</rss>
